<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="dietplan1"><title><b>DAILY DIET PLAN</b></title>\n
        \n<b>A. Breakfast :</b>
\ni. Non-vegetarian : 3 egg white and 1 yolk omelet with veggies, plain yoghurt and 1/2 a fruit.
\nii. Vegetarian : Sweet potato, pancakes, muesli with oats, yoghurt, dates and berries.
        \n<b>B. Lunch :</b>
\ni. Non-vegetarian : Chicken breast, quinoa, mixed veggies, mainly carbohydrates and proteins type of food.
\nii. Vegetarian : Cucumber, pea and lettuce soup, salads, beetroots and broccolis.
        \n<b>C. Dinner :</b>
\ni. Non-vegetarian : Salmon and mixed veggies, different types of vegetables, mainly fats and proteins type of food.
\nii. Vegetarian : Guacamole and mango salad with black beans, spinach and fenugreek dishes, cheese and sweet potato curry.
    </string>
    <string name="dietplan2"><title><b>7 DAYS DIET PLAN</b></title>\n
        \n<b>A. Day 1 – Fruits : People can eat a range of fruits, especially melons and citrus fruits, but should avoid bananas.</b>
\ni. breakfast: 1 medium apple or 1 bowl of mixed berries
\nii. snack: 1 bowl of cantaloupe or an orange
\niii. lunch: 1 bowl of watermelon
\niv. snack: 1 orange
\nv. dinner: 1 pear or 1 bowl of kiwi
\nvi. snack: 1 bowl of mixed berries
        \n\n<b>B. Day 2 — Vegetables : Start the day with a sweet potato or baked potato, but limit potato intake to breakfast only. People can eat vegetables raw or cooked.</b>
\ni. breakfast: 1 sweet potato or 1 baked potato
\nii. snack: 1 bowl of cabbage
\niii. lunch: a mixed salad containing lettuce, tomatoes, carrots, and cucumber
\niv. snack: 1 bowl of steamed or raw broccoli
\nv. dinner: 1 bowl of kale or arugula with asparagus
\nvi. snack: 1 bowl of sliced cucumbers
        \n\n<b>C. Day 3 — Fruit and vegetables : People can eat the same foods as days 1 and 2, avoiding bananas and potatoes.</b>
\ni. breakfast: 1 apple or 1 bowl of watermelon
\nii. snack: 1 bowl of cherry tomatoes
\niii. lunch: a mixed salad
\niv. snack: 1 bowl of sliced cucumbers
\nv. dinner: 1 kale salad with carrots and cucumbers and 1 bowl of strawberries on the side
\nvi. snack: 1 apple
        \n\n<b>D. Day 4 — Bananas and milk : Eat bananas either whole or in a smoothie with milk and ice. No other fruits or vegetables are allowed, but people can also eat wonder soup.</b>
\ni. breakfast: 2 bananas and 1 glass of milk
\nii. snack: 1 smoothie containing banana and skim milk
        \niii. lunch: 1 bowl of wonder soup
\niv. snack: 1 smoothie containing banana and skim milk
\nv. dinner: wonder soup and 1 banana
        \n\n<b>E. Day 5 — Meat : Eat 20 ounces (oz) of either beef, chicken, or fish. Vegetarians can replace meat with cottage cheese or brown rice.</b>
\ni. breakfast: 5–6 oz serving of meat and 2 whole tomatoes
\nii. lunch: 7–8 oz serving of meat with 2 whole tomatoes
\niii. dinner: 5–6 oz serving of meat with 2 whole tomatoes
\niv. snacks: wonder soup or freshly pressed tomato juice
\nv. an additional 4 cups of water
        \n\n<b>F. Day 6 — Meat and vegetables : Eat 20 oz of meat and unlimited raw or cooked vegetables, excluding potatoes and tomatoes. Vegetarians can have cottage cheese or brown rice in place of meat.</b>
\ni. breakfast: 5–6 oz serving of meat with 1 bowl of vegetables
\nii. lunch: 7–8 oz serving of meat with 1 bowl of vegetables
\niii. dinner: 5–6 oz serving of meat with wonder soup
\niv. snacks: wonder soup
        \n\n<b>G. Day 7 — Rice, fruit, and vegetables : Eat fruit, vegetables, and brown rice. The diet plan for this day permits sugar-free juice.</b>
\ni. breakfast: 1 bowl of brown rice and 1 orange or a bowl of watermelon
\nii. lunch: 1 bowl of brown rice and 1 glass of sugar-free fruit juice
\niii. dinner: 1 bowl of brown rice with 1 bowl of raw or cooked vegetables
        \niv. snacks: berries, citrus fruits, or wonder soup
    </string>
    <string name="dietplan3"><title><b>WEIGHT LOSS TIPS</b></title>\n
\n1. Try Intermittent Fasting
\n2. Drink Water, Especially Before Meals
\n3. Eat Eggs For Breakfast
\n4. Drink Coffee (Preferably Black)
\n5. Take a Glucomannan Supplement
\n6. Cut Back on Added Sugar
\n7. Drink Green Tea
\n8. Eat Less Refined Carbs
\n9. Go on a Low-Carb Diet
\n10. Eat More Fiber
\n11. Exercise Portion Control or Count Calories
\n12. Keep Healthy Food Around in Case You Get Hungry
\n13. Take Probiotic Supplements
\n14. Eat Spicy Foods
\n15. Do Aerobic Exercise
    </string>


</resources>